

Kasra Mahsouli

FullStack Web Developer

My Contact

kasramahsouli@gmail.com

(+989178100755

IRAN, Shiraz

Professional Skills

- React js
- Next js
- · Node is
- Express is
- Typescript
- Javascript
- Mongo db
- MySql
- Html
- Css
- Sass / Less
- Material ui
- Tailwind css
- Bootstrap

Education Background

Public University of Azad Certificate : **Bachelor of IT** React Certification from Udemy

Portfolio

www.chiliscript.de

Special Skills

English proficiency equivalent to C1 **German** proficiency equivalent to A2

Native Language: Persian

About Me

Web Developer with 5 years of experience and a proven ability to adapt in both self-starting and collaborative environments. Eager to obtain a challenging position at a prestigious company that will expand my learning and build upon my developer skills.

Marital status : Married Date of Birth : Sep 25th 1994

Professional Experience

Anabin Securities inc. (Canada) / Mern Stacker

March, 2023 - Present (Ongoing Project)

Key responsibilities:

- Currently working with development, testing, and deployment tools such as Git, Github Actions, Gitlab CI CD, Docker, Docker compose, and Kubernetes based on project needs and scale.
- Developing websites using various frameworks and programming Technologies including Typescript, Reactjs, Nodejs, Nextjs(v13), Vite / Webpack, MongoDB, Expressjs, ReactQuery, Jest , Websocket, Socketlo, Mongoose, Redux Toolkit, Docker, Git / Github, Threejs, React Fiber, Framer Motion.

Myzel inc. (IRAN) / Junior FullStack Developer

January, 2020 - March, 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Changed the User interface along with integration of new functionalities both on the front and on the server side.
- The transformation from Junior Frontend Developer to Junior Fullstacker with access to handle the Automation process of CI CD pipelines on Linux VPS Server and AWS Cloud Server.
- Conducted and participated in project planning and scheduling, design discussions, and provided assistance during testing.
- Reduced IT Department costs by 30% by eliminating unnecessary servers and minimized workload put upon remaining servers.

HillzDealer inc. (Canada) / Junior Frontend Developer

July, 2019 - January, 2020

Key responsibilities:

- Met with the development team to discuss user interface ideas and applications.
- Troubleshot interface software and debugged application codes.
- Designed and developed new custom components to meet project requirements.

Chadko inc. (IRAN) / Frontend Developer Internship

Augest, 2018 - April, 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Built reusable components through functional components.
- Worked with Bootstrap, Next and React.